{
  "status": true,
  "data": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "title": "Quiz",
      "details": [
        {
          "question": "Which type of network threat is intended to prevent authorized users from accessing resources?",
          "options": [
            "DoS attacks",
            "access attacks",
            "reconnaissance attacks",
            "trust exploitation"
          ],
          "answer": "DoS attacks"
        },
        {
          "question": "An email claiming that you have won the lottery, as long as you fill out the corresponding information, is an example of what type social engineering attack?",
          "options": [
            "Baiting ",
            "Phishing",
            "PiggyBacking",
            "Baiting"
          ],
          "answer": "Phishing"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which malicious code attack is self-contained and tries to exploit a specific vulnerability in a system being attacked?",
          "options": [
            "virus",
            "worm",
            "Trojan horse",
            "social engineering"
          ],
          "answer": "worm"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the purpose of the network security accounting function?",
          "options": [
            "to require users to prove who they are",
            "to determine which resources a user can access",
            "to keep track of the actions of a user",
            "to provide challenge and response questions"
          ],
          "answer": "to keep track of the actions of a user"
        },
        {
          "question": "_______means the protection of data from modification by unknown usres",
          "options": [
            "Confidentiality",
            "Integrity",
            "Authentication",
            ""
          ],
          "answer": "Integrity"
        },
        {
          "question": "When integrity is lacking in a security system,________ occurs",
          "options": [
            "Database hacking",
            "Data deletion",
            "Data tampering",
            "Data leakage"
          ],
          "answer": "Data tampering"
        },
        {
          "question": "What are the types of malware?",
          "options": [
            "horse",
            "worm",
            "lion",
            ""
          ],
          "answer": "worm"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is trojan horse",
          "options": [
            "A Trojan Horse program has the appearance of having a useful and desired function",
            "A Trojan Horse neither replicates nor copies itself, but causes damage or compromises the security of the computer",
            "A Trojan Horse must be sent by someone or carried by another program and may arrive in the form of a joke program or software of some sort",
            "All of the above"
          ],
          "answer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which of the following is a program capable of continually replicating with little or no user intervention?",
          "options": [
            "Virus",
            "Rootkit",
            "worm",
            "Trojan horse"
          ],
          "answer": "Virus"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which of these is how to properly avoid becoming a victim of social engineering?",
          "options": [
            "Research the fact",
            "Delete any request for financial information or passwords",
            "Reject request for help",
            "All of the above"
          ],
          "answer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
          "question": "Phishing attacks hide themselves using these techniques except:",
          "options": [
            "Tiny URLs",
            "Domain names with close spelling to legitimate sites",
            "Real logos and convincing prose",
            "Links to legitimate sites that has been compromised to deliver malware",
            "None of the above"
          ],
          "answer": "None of the above"
        },
        {
          "question": "Having physical access to ones computer, even if the computer is locked, may enable the following attack except this one:",
          "options": [
            "Steal ones password",
            "Install key logger",
            "Install malware",
            "Copy files",
            "None of the above"
          ],
          "answer": "Steal ones password"
        },
        {
          "question": "In social engineering, attacker use the following techniques to gain victim's trust except",
          "options": [
            "Appear to be an expert",
            "Asking for help",
            "Dressed appropriately",
            "Speak with certain accents",
            "Directly ask for sensitive information"
          ],
          "answer": "Directly ask for sensitive information"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which of the following is a valid difference between a Virus and a Spyware?",
          "options": [
            "Spyware damages data and also steals sensitive private information",
            "Virus damages data, spyware steals sensitive private information",
            "Spyware damages data, Virus steals sensitive private information",
            "Virus damages data and also steals sensitive private information"
          ],
          "answer": "Virus damages data, spyware steals sensitive private information"
        },
        {
          "question": "What happens during the TCP attacks, Denial of service?",
          "options": [
            "A virus is sent to disable their dos prompt",
            "Viruses are sent to their ISP to deny them tech support",
            "A worm is loaded onto the victimâ€™s computer to disable their keyboard",
            "Information is repeatedly sent to the victim to consume their system resources, causing them to shut down"
          ],
          "answer": "Information is repeatedly sent to the victim to consume their system resources, causing them to shut down"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}